wowmb.net 2012-09-19

# The Warlocks Den - Privacy Statement

|  | 

Please Register to Remove these Ads 

|  Top 5 Stats   
---  
Latest Posts | Latest Forum News  
| Thread |   |  Date, Time |  Posted By  
---|---|---|---  
 [solo onyxia](http://wowmb.net/forums/f49/33236-solo_onyxia/) | [ ▼](http://wowmb.net/forums/f49/33236-solo_onyxia/) |  18-09, 23:32 |  [hefron](http://wowmb.net/forums/members/hefron/)  
 [solo'ing Kael'thas in tempest...](http://wowmb.net/forums/f49/41238-soloing_kaelthas_tempest_keep/) | [ ▼](http://wowmb.net/forums/f49/41238-soloing_kaelthas_tempest_keep/) |  18-09, 23:25 |  [hefron](http://wowmb.net/forums/members/hefron/)  
 [Grimoire of Sac---I must be...](http://wowmb.net/forums/f9/43041-grimoire_sac_i_must_blind/) | [ ▼](http://wowmb.net/forums/f9/43041-grimoire_sac_i_must_blind/) |  18-09, 10:42 |  [Tragik](http://wowmb.net/forums/members/tragik/)  
 [Gearing up from heroics in...](http://wowmb.net/forums/f22/43424-gearing_up_heroics_mists_pandaria/) | [ ▼](http://wowmb.net/forums/f22/43424-gearing_up_heroics_mists_pandaria/) |  18-09, 04:25 |  [Aghast](http://wowmb.net/forums/members/aghast/)  
 [Affli vs Destro vs Demo in...](http://wowmb.net/forums/f9/43374-affli_vs_destro_vs_demo_5_04_a/) | [ ▼](http://wowmb.net/forums/f9/43374-affli_vs_destro_vs_demo_5_04_a/) |  17-09, 22:23 |  [Scathbais](http://wowmb.net/forums/members/scathbais/)  
 [To glyph or not to glyph.....](http://wowmb.net/forums/f9/43211-glyph_not_glyph_mop/) | [ ▼](http://wowmb.net/forums/f9/43211-glyph_not_glyph_mop/) |  17-09, 22:19 |  [Scathbais](http://wowmb.net/forums/members/scathbais/)  
 [Professions for a new warlock](http://wowmb.net/forums/f10/32119-professions_new_warlock/) | [ ▼](http://wowmb.net/forums/f10/32119-professions_new_warlock/) |  16-09, 04:48 |  [D1RE](http://wowmb.net/forums/members/d1re/)  
 [Demonology pvp](http://wowmb.net/forums/f43/41246-demonology_pvp/) | [ ▼](http://wowmb.net/forums/f43/41246-demonology_pvp/) |  12-09, 23:08 |  [marcevil](http://wowmb.net/forums/members/marcevil/)  
 [Weapon change?](http://wowmb.net/forums/f22/43321-weapon_change/) | [ ▼](http://wowmb.net/forums/f22/43321-weapon_change/) |  12-09, 11:47 |  [Owewa](http://wowmb.net/forums/members/owewa/)  
 [This place is getting annoying](http://wowmb.net/forums/f8/43072-place_getting_annoying/) | [ ▼](http://wowmb.net/forums/f8/43072-place_getting_annoying/) |  12-09, 10:46 |  [Supernex](http://wowmb.net/forums/members/supernex/)  
|  [Thanks to the active...](http://wowmb.net/forums/f71/42812-thanks_active_reporters_den/) |  14-08  
---|---  
 [Urgent: Important Security...](http://wowmb.net/forums/f71/42779-urgent_important_security_update/) |  10-08  
 [Huge Warlock buff!!](http://wowmb.net/forums/f71/42777-huge_warlock_buff/) |  09-08  
 [Mists of Pandaria release...](http://wowmb.net/forums/f71/42740-mists_pandaria_release_date_has_been_confirmed/) |  25-07  
 [Some Warlock Q&A](http://wowmb.net/forums/f71/42722-some_warlock_q/) |  23-06  
Latest Blog Entries  
---|---  

**Our Commitment to Privacy:  
**Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. 

**Notification of Changes:**  
The Warlocks Den reserves the right to update and amend this policy as it is deemed necessary or appropriate to do so. Please check back often to be appraised of any changes. This version was updated on July 2nd, 2006.

**Guest Information:**  
As a guest, no personal information is collected or retained by the site. When viewing the site, the server will collect "non-personal" information from you, such as your browser type, your operating system, and your IP Address for statistical information only. This information ("Non-Personal Information") cannot be easily used to personally identify you.

**Forum Registration and Member Information:**  
When registering on The Warlocks Den forums, you are required to enter in certain information (“Member Info”) to distinguish yourself from other members. Member Info consists of such things as a user name, a password and email address. 

When posting a new thread, or reply to an existing thread on the forums, the information is allocated against your user name. At the time of the post, your IP address is also logged,   
Viewable only by the Administrator.

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:**  
If you are a registered member of the forums, you can access all the information we collect online and maintain it through your [User CP](http://forums.wowmb.net/usercp.php). Accounts are never deleted from the database, however should you require your user information to be removed, you can contact the Administrator. Please note the user name will stay, this will only effect personal information such as an email address.

**Email:**

> _**Contact Us  
>  **_When utilizing the [Contact Us](http://forums.wowmb.net/sendmessage.php) form, it provides the name, email and IP address of the sender, along with the information provided in the body of the form. If you are logged in as a member of the forum, it will also provide the User name and ID number.
> 
> _**Standard Email  
>  **_When using standard email to contact the Administrator by the email address provided, it provides the name and email address of the sender along with email header information and the context of the email. 

Regardless of the choice of contact made by a visitor or member of the site, all information contained is regarded as private and confidential and will not be shared unless deemed as a threat to the site or requested by any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request. The user name provided may be used on the website to provide a news update or information post. We retain all email correspondence indefinitely in order to improve our services according to customer feedback.

**Donating:**  
The Warlocks Den allows monetary donations from its members via PayPal. Information relating to the donator is provided to the Administrator, and includes the name, shipping address and email provided when making the donation. This information is only used to match the donator to a user name on the forums in order to allocate them to the proper (“Donators”) user group. 

PayPal also provide the information relating to their [Privacy Policy](https://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr) via their website.

**The Warlocks Den Store:**  
The Warlocks Den uses the facilities of CafePress.com to distribute T-Shirts, Coffee Mugs and other items for sale. Should you choose to make a purchase, CafePress.com willcollect personal Information to identify you individually, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, credit card number, and financial information. 

CafePress.com will also collect "non-personal" information from you, such as your browser type, the URL of the previous web site you visited, your ISP, operating system, and your IP Address. This information ("Non-Personal Information") cannot be easily used to personally identify you.

By using the CafePress.com Web Site you are accepting the practices outlined in their [ Privacy Policy](http://www.cafepress.com/cp/info/help/privacy.aspx?s=warlocksden). If you have any questions or comments, please contact them at: [privacy@cafepress.com](mailto:privacy@cafepress.com)

**Advertisements:**  
This site currently uses Google Adsense for its advertisements. Please view their [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy.html) for more information. 

**“Other” Sites:**  
The Warlocks Den is not responsible for the privacy practices of any web sites that may be linked. We encourage you to become familiar with the privacy practices of these sites before you provide them with personal information. The Warlocks Den will never purposely link to sites that distribute person information, nor will it provide any information for use. Should you feel a site linked violates this statement, please contact the Administrator.

**How to Contact Us:**  
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please email us at [privacy@wowmb.net](mailto:privacy@wowmb.net).
